Seward, Ralph T. Additional Arbitration Files 5779
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Ralph T. Seward Additional Arbitration Files
1980-1987
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seward, Ralph T.
5779
15 cubic feet
15 linear ft.
Records (documents), case files.
Collective labor agreements
3124431
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 02, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 02, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Arbitrator and mediator; member, National Mediation Service, National Defense Mediation Board; impartial umpire for cases involving the dairy, auto and steel industries, among others.
Ralph Seward (BA., Cornell University, 1927; MA., New York University, 1931; LLB., Columbia University, 1935) served as an attorney with the National Labor Relations Board (1936-1937) and was executive secretary (1937-1939) and general counsel (1939) of the New York State Labor Relations Board. He also served as chairman of the Board of Immigration Appeals, U.S. Department of Justice (1939-1941), as executive secretary, National Defense Mediation Board (1941-1942), and as associate public member of the U.S. National War Labor Board (1942) before going into private practice as an arbitrator and mediator. In addition to chairing two Emergency Boards of the National Mediation Service, Seward was impartial chairman for the metropolitan New York milk industry (1942-1944); impartial umpire for General Motors Corporation and the United Automobile Workers (1944-1947); chairman of the Board of Conciliation and Arbitration of United States Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America (1947-1949); impartial umpire for International Harvester Company and United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America (1949-1951); impartial umpire for Bethlehem Steel Corporation and the United Steelworkers of America (1952); and arbitrator and/or mediator in various other cases.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5064: U.S. Emergency Board No. 169 Transcript of Proceedings and Exhibits 5113: Ralph T. Seward Arbitration Transcripts and Exhibits 5328: Ralph T. Seward Papers 5700: Ralph T. Seward Additional Arbitration Files 5970: Ralph Seward Additional Papers
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; Seward, Ralph T.1907-; Communications Workers of America; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers. Local 827; Illinois Bell Telephone Company; New Jersey Bell Telephone Company; New York Telephone Company; Inland Steel Company; United Steelworkers of America. Local 1010
3124431
- American Postal Workers Union-Bermuda Broadcasting Company (Box 1)
  - American Postal Workers Union, Health Plan Department versus OPEIU Local 2 - Issue: Just Cause for Termination, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    January 3, 1986
  - AT&T versus Communication Workers of America - Issue: Payment of Night differential, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    September 3, 1980
  - Anchor Hocking Corporation versus Glass Bottle Blowers Association, Local 200 - Issue: Discharge of Grievants, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    March 3, 1982
  - Anchor Hocking Corporation versus Glass, Pottery, Plastics and Allied Workers Industrial Union - Issue: Suspension and Discharge of Grievant, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    May 12, 1983
  - Amstar Corporation versus United Food and Commercial Workers Union, Local 392 - Issue: Discharge for Assault, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    September 9, 1985
  - Babcock and Wilcox Company, Power Generation Group versus International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Local Lodge 901 - Issue: Three Shift Scheduling of Maintenance Employees, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    January 16, 1981
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania versus Federation of Telephone Workers - Issue: Job Classification and Assignment of Work Duties, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    April 21, 1985
  - Bermuda Broadcasting Company, Limited versus Bermuda Industrial Union - Issue: Contract Negotiations Disputes, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    September 2, 1984
- Bermuda Butler Aviation Limited-General Telephone Company of the Southeast (Box 2)
  - Bermuda Butler Aviation Limited versus Bermuda Industrial Union, Air Services Division - Issue: 1. Hours of Work and 2. Holiday Pay Relating to Full-time and Part-time Employees, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    December 16, 1982
  - Bethlehem Steel Corporation (Johnstown Plant) versus USWA Local 7400 - Issue: Discharge Related to Continuous Service, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    April 13, 1984
  - District of Columbia Department of Corrections versus AFGE Local 1550 - Issue: Suspension for Violation of Departmental Regulation, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    April 16, 1981
  - District of Columbia Board of Education versus American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Local 2093 - Issue: Termination for Unauthorized Absences, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    September 30, 1985
  - DELMARVA Power and Light Company of Maryland versus IBEW Local 1307 - Issue: Working Auxiliary Operators in a Fuel Handler Classification, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    April 22, 1981
  - Georgia Pacific Corporation versus United Paperworkers International Union (UPIU) Local 706 - Issue: Determining Qualifications of Line Adjusters, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    June 22, 1981
  - General Telephone Company of the Southeast versus Communication Workers of America (CWA) Local 10972 - Issue: Violation of Vacation Rights, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    June 19, 1981
- Illinois Bell Telephone Company - Inland Steel Company (Box 3)
  - Illinois Bell Telephone Company versus CWA, District 5 - Issue: Just Cause for Discharge, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    April 6, 1981
  - Illinois Bell Telephone Company versus CWA - Issue: Severity of Penalty, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    May 11, 1981
  - Inland Steel Company versus USWA Local 1010 - Issue: Just Cause for Discharge, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    November 30, 1982
  - Inland Steel Company versus USWA Local 1010 - Issue: Unwarranted Discipline, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    December 17, 1982
  - Inland Steel Company versus USWA Local 1010 - Issue: Discharge for Repeated Absenteeism, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    January 5, 1983
- New England Telephone - New York Telephone Company (Box 4)
  - New England Telephone versus IBEW; Hearing - Issue: Payment for Absence During Training (Grievance Withdrawn), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    April 28, 1983
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company versus IBEW Local 827 - Issue: Just Cause for Discharge, Remedy, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    April 10, 1982
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company versus IBEW Local 827 - Issue: Promotion of Grievant, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    November 29, 1984
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company versus IBEW Local 827 - Grievance Withdrawn, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    February 25, 1987
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company versus IBEW Local 827 - Grievance Withdrawn, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    February 5, 1986
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company versus IBEW Local 827 - Grievance Withdrawn, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    October 15, 1984
  - New York Daily News versus New York Typographical Union, Local 6 - Issue: Interest on Retrograde Wages, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    July 8, 1981
- New York Telephone Company (Box 5)
  - New York Telephone Company versus CWA, District 1 - Issue: Just Cause for Discharge, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    March 6, 1984
  - New York Telephone Company versus CWA Local 1122 - Issue: Supervisory Actions Challenged as a Prohibited Invasion of the Collective Bargaining Unit, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    September 20, 1983
  - New York Telephone Company versus CWA - Grievance Withdrawn, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    March 12, 1984
- New York Telephone Company (Box 6)
  - New York Telephone Company versus VWA - Issue: Alleged Denial of Transfer (Grievance Withdrawn), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    October 15, 1982
  - New York Telephone Company versus CWA Local 1105 - Grievance Withdrawn, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    January 23, 1986
  - New York Telephone Company versus CWA - Issue: Working Management-ASCC Computer (Grievance Settled), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    May 15, 1985
- Safeway Stores, Incorporated - Western Electric (Box 7)
  - Safeway Stores, Incorporated versus United Food and Commercial Workers Local 400 - Issue: Discharge for Excessive Absenteeism, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    February 18, 1981
  - Southern Bell Telephone and Telegraph Company versus CWA - Issue: Selection for Job Vacancy, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    August 15, 1983
  - Titanium Metals Corporation of America versus USWA Local 4856 - Issue: Contracting Out Work, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    January 19, 1982
  - Titanium Metals Corporation of America versus USWA Local 5644 - Issue: Application of Company's Drug and Alcohol Rehabilitation Program, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    April 2, 1984
  - United States Postal Service, Research and Development Laboratory versus American Postal Workers Union - Issue: Resolution of Issues for Bargaining of New Agreement Including Salaries and Wages, Separability, and Duration, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    May 12, 1982 Additional US Post Office information - see box 15
  - United States Government Printing Office versus Washington Government Photo Offset Union Number 538 - Issue: Extension of Training Program, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    March 27, 1981
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company (VEPCO) versus IBEW System Council U-1 - Issue: Filling an Entrance Position and Arbitrability of Grievance, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    May 18, 1984
  - Washington Gas Light Company versus International Union of Gas Workers - Grievance Withdrawn, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    February 18, 1982
  - Western Electric versus Communication Equipment Workers - Grievance Withdrawn, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    October 15, 1980
- Railroad Dispute (Box 8)
  - Railroad Disputes (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Railroad Dispute (Box 9)
  - Railroad Disputes (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Railroad Dispute (Box 10)
  - Railroad Disputes (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Documents and Materials for Railroads and General Motors (Box 11)
  - Documents and Materials for Railroads and General Motors (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Documents and Materials for Railroads and General Motors (Box 12)
  - Documents and Materials for Railroads and General Motors (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Basic Steel Incentive Study (Box 13)
  - Basic Steel Incentive Study (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Basic Steel Incentive Study (Box 14)
  - Basic Steel Incentive Study (Box 14, Folder 1)
- United Postal Workers transcripts and information (Box 15)
  - United Postal Workers (Box 15, Folder 1)
    transcripts and information